<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam, Daat Hero on Sam&#39;s Emotions</title>
    <link>/blog/sam-series/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sam, Daat Hero on Sam&#39;s Emotions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/sam-series/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sam&#39;s Phone Call</title>
      <link>/blog/sam-series/01-sam-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sam-series/01-sam-series/</guid>
      <description>This story is borrowed from Paulina Sliwa (2012)’s Defense of Moral Testimony.
 Sam is standing at the shore of a lake when he sees a child beginning to drown. He believes that saving the child would be the good thing to do but it would involve ruining his new expensive suit. He cannot decide what to do and there is no one else at the lake, so he decides to call a friend whom he takes to be reliable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah and Sam</title>
      <link>/blog/sam-series/02-sam-sarah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sam-series/02-sam-sarah/</guid>
      <description>Sarah and her fiance Sam are planning a wedding and both their families have agreed to contribute towards it. However, Sarah’s family is considerably less wealthy than Sam’s. Sarah’s family offered an amount that is less than half of the wedding costs and Sam and Sarah are wondering whether it would be fair to let Sam’s family pay more than Sarah’s. Initially they had wanted their wedding to be the envy of the three powers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam and Mary</title>
      <link>/blog/sam-series/03-sam-mary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sam-series/03-sam-mary/</guid>
      <description>Mary Mary has always enjoyed eating meat but recently has accepted a contract to deliver 1000 tons of animal product to Hutton Orbital in Alpha Centauri.12 From the moment she landed in the ship hanger at London Relay, her senses were assaulted by the aromas and sounds of hundreds of thousands of species, clamoring fruitlessly against their constraints, their natures never for a minute allowing them to rest, in the peaceful acceptance of their impending fate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam the Hero</title>
      <link>/blog/sam-series/04-sam-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sam-series/04-sam-hero/</guid>
      <description>The idea of emunah to daat I borrowed from Samuel Lebens in his delightfully interesting paper: Amen to Daat1: On the Foundations of Jewish Epistemology.
Silently, the massive imperial structure traversed the sky line, bathing the land below it in a void less mass, shapeless as it was, the shadow along the ground struck fear into its inhabitants, earth bound as they were, they knew, no rather they believed that there was no escaping the wrath of the mitrathi; that is until a whisper began to grow throughout their ranks: it is better to die on our feet, rather than live on their knees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
